<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Perfectly Cromulent</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Perfectly Cromulent</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 14:23:02 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We Should Just Stay Friends</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/we-should-just-stay-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 14:23:02 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/we-should-just-stay-friends/</guid>
      <description>Oh, I think we should just stay friends. Now Fry, it&amp;rsquo;s been a few years since medical school, so remind me. Disemboweling in your species: fatal or non-fatal? We can&amp;rsquo;t compete with Mom! Her company is big and evil! Ours is small and neutral! Hey, you add a one and two zeros to that or we walk!
Hey! I&amp;rsquo;m a porno-dealing monster, what do I care what you think? Kids have names?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youve Killed Me</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/youve-killed-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 14:22:25 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/youve-killed-me/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve killed me! Oh, you&amp;rsquo;ve killed me! Kif might! Wow, you got that off the Internet? In my day, the Internet was only used to download pornography. The key to victory is discipline, and that means a well made bed. You will practice until you can make your bed in your sleep.
You&amp;rsquo;ve killed me! Oh, you&amp;rsquo;ve killed me! Yes. You gave me a dollar and some candy. Yes! In your face, Gandhi!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last Night Was a Mistake</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/last-night-was-a-mistake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 14:21:25 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/last-night-was-a-mistake/</guid>
      <description>Look, last night was a mistake. Yep, I remember. They came in last at the Olympics, then retired to promote alcoholic beverages! Kids have names? That&amp;rsquo;s right, baby. I ain&amp;rsquo;t your loverboy Flexo, the guy you love so much. You even love anyone pretending to be him!
I had more, but you go ahead. And when we woke up, we had these bodies. Oh, I don&amp;rsquo;t have time for this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Dont Need to Drink</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/i-dont-need-to-drink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 14:20:34 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/i-dont-need-to-drink/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t &amp;lsquo;need&amp;rsquo; to drink. I can quit anytime I want! You lived before you met me?! I could if you hadn&amp;rsquo;t turned on the light and shut off my stereo. Eeeee! Now say &amp;ldquo;nuclear wessels&amp;rdquo;! Fry, we have a crate to deliver. Yep, I remember. They came in last at the Olympics, then retired to promote alcoholic beverages!
No! Don&amp;rsquo;t jump! Have you ever tried just turning off the TV, sitting down with your children, and hitting them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://example.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 14:01:47 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Perfectly Cromulent is the home of Nav, a full stack developer with experience in marketing and project management.
Why Perfectly Cromulent? Short Answer: The Simpsons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>